export default [
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f950514",
    correctAnswer: "underground water",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "the cosmos or our place in it",
      "Tibet",
      "the effect of evolution on ethology",
    ],
    question: "What is Hydrogeology the study of?",
    tags: ["words", "science"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "medium",
    regions: [],
  },
  {
    category: "Music",
    id: "622a1c397cc59eab6f950cb1",
    correctAnswer: "Pink Floyd",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Wings", "Rudimental", "The Alan Parsons Project"],
    question:
      "Which English rock band released the studio album 'The Final Cut'?",
    tags: ["music"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "hard",
    regions: [],
  },
  {
    category: "History",
    id: "62611ffd4b176d54800e3d7f",
    correctAnswer: "1985",
    incorrectAnswers: ["1979", "1991", "1997"],
    question: "When was the Live Aid concert?",
    tags: ["events", "history"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "hard",
    regions: [],
  },
  {
    category: "Food & Drink",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f95027c",
    correctAnswer: "Florida ",
    incorrectAnswers: ["South America", "France", "Mexico"],
    question: "Where Does Key Lime Pie Come From?",
    tags: ["food", "food_and_drink"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "medium",
    regions: [],
  },
  {
    category: "Film & TV",
    id: "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fb31",
    correctAnswer: "No Country for Old Men",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Atonement", "Juno", "Michael Clayton"],
    question: "Which film won the Academy Award for Best Picture in 2007?",
    tags: ["academy_awards", "film", "film_and_tv"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "hard",
    regions: [],
  },
  {
    category: "Geography",
    id: "62602d254b176d54800e3c82",
    correctAnswer: "China",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Mongolia", "India", "Australia"],
    question: "Where would you find the city of Beijing?",
    tags: ["cities", "general_knowledge", "geography"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "easy",
    regions: [],
  },
  {
    category: "Society & Culture",
    id: "6266e68aff2394bd44dee052",
    correctAnswer: "Seven",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Two", "Green", "Ten"],
    question: "In Italian, what is the meaning of the word 'sette'?",
    tags: ["language", "translations", "society_and_culture"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "hard",
    regions: [],
  },
  {
    category: "Arts & Literature",
    id: "622a1c397cc59eab6f950e05",
    correctAnswer: "Lewis Carroll",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Enid Blyton", "George Orwell", "Charles Dickens"],
    question: "Which author wrote 'Through the Looking-Glass'?",
    tags: ["arts_and_literature"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "easy",
    regions: [],
  },
  {
    category: "Film & TV",
    id: "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fc49",
    correctAnswer: "\"Toto, I've a feeling we're not in Kansas anymore.\"",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      '"Frankly, my dear, I don\'t give a damn."',
      '"I’ve been a poor man and I’ve been a rich man. And I choose rich every f****** time!"',
      '"I love the smell of napalm in the morning."',
    ],
    question: "Which of these quotes is from the film 'The Wizard of Oz'?",
    tags: ["film", "quotes", "general_knowledge", "film_and_tv"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "medium",
    regions: [],
  },
  {
    category: "History",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f9503ac",
    correctAnswer: "Germany",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Switzerland", "Denmark", "France"],
    question: "Which country was first to operate an old age pension scheme?",
    tags: ["history"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "hard",
    regions: [],
  },
];
